https://xm655.com/cookie-policy-uk/

Cookie policy (UK) | XM655 Maintenance and Preservation Society
Cookie policy
Search for:
Cookie policy (UK)
This Cookie Policy was last updated on 07/07/2020 and applies to citizens of the United Kingdom.1. IntroductionOur website, https://xm655.com (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on "Save preferences", you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.5.1 Manage your consent settings6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.7. Placed cookiesComplianz
We use Complianz for cookie consent management.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
cmplz_event_*
365 days
Store cookie consent preferences
cmplz_choice
Sharing
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Statement.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics for website statistics.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics (anonymous)
_ga
2 years
Store a unique user ID
_gid
1 day
Count and track pageviews
_gat
1 minute
Filter requests from bots
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
YouTube
We use YouTube for video display.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
PREF
1 year
Store and track visits across websites
YSC
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Statement.
PayPal
We use PayPal for payment processing.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
paypal
persistent
Provide fraud prevention
__paypal_storage__
persistent
Store account details
ts_c
3 years
Provide fraud prevention
Sharing
For more information, please read the PayPal Privacy Statement.
WP Do Not Track
We use WP Do Not Track for cookie consent management.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
dont_track_me
1 year
Store 'do not track' signals
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Google reCAPTCHA
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
rc::c
session
Filter requests from bots
rc::b
session
Filter requests from bots
rc::a
persistent
Filter requests from bots
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Statement.
Roundcube
We use Roundcube for miscellaneous.
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
roundcube_cookies
Functional
roundcube_sessauth
session
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Dailymotion
We use Dailymotion for video display.
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
ts
v1st
hist
dmvk
Statistics
damd
session
Store performed actions on the website
Sharing
For more information, please read the Dailymotion Privacy Statement.
adobe marketing cloud
We use adobe marketing cloud for marketing automation (automated email marketing).
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
s_vi
10 years
Count and track pageviews
dpm
Sharing
For more information, please read the adobe marketing cloud Privacy Statement.
Miscellaneous
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
tcb_google_fonts
eMember_in_use
wp_*
OTelJS.ClientId
timezone
webmailsession
cpsession
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO)).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:655 Maintenance and Preservation Society
Wellesbourne Airfield, Loxley Lane, Wellesbourne
CV35 9EU Warwick
United Kingdom
Website: https://xm655.com
Email: DataProtectionOfficer@xm655.com
This Cookie Policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 08/10/2020
Cookie policy (UK)
Shopping Cart Cart is empty (0)
Member Login
Username
Password
Forgot Password?
Forgot Password?
Join Us
